shareitforpc.online 2018-12-03

# Legal Notice, Privacy Policy and Cookies - Shareitforpc.online

## Use of Cookies

This website may use cookies (these are small text files that the server sends to the computer of the person accessing the page). It is a technique commonly used on the Internet to carry out certain functions that are considered essential for the correct functioning and visualization of the site.

The cookies used on this website are, in any case, temporary and under no circumstances will cookies be used to collect personal information.

From this website, you may be redirected to third-party website content. Since Shareitforpc.online cannot always control the content introduced by third parties on its websites, Shareitforpc.online assumes no responsibility for such content. In any case, we commit ourselves to the immediate withdrawal of any content that could contravene national or international legislation, morality or public order, proceeding to the immediate withdrawal of the redirection to this website, informing the competent authorities of the content in question.

## How to block cookies

If you want to know the cookies generated by each web site you browse and block them in an easy way, there is a Firefox plug-in called [Ghostery](https://addons.mozilla.org/en-US/firefox/addon/ghostery/).

The settings for each of the main browsers can be found on these pages of their support media:

  * Safari: <https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT201265>
  * Firefox: <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>
  * Chrome: <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en-en>
  * Opera: <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/privacy/>
  * Internet Explorer: <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/260971/description-of-cookies>

By using this website, you consent to the Use of Cookies in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

## Data Hosting

For technical reasons and quality of service, the blog www.shareitforpc.online is hosted on the servers of Raiola Networks ([Privacy Policy – Legal Notice](https://raiolanetworks.es/aviso-legal/)).

## Google Adsense

Advertising through Google AdSense is used on this site.

Google uses the[ DoubleClick DART](https://www.doubleclickbygoogle.com/) cookie for ads placed on publishers’ websites that display AdSense ads for content.

When an end user accesses a website of the AdSense publisher and sees an ad or clicks on it, a cookie may be placed in your browser. The data collected from these cookies is used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage ads on their sites and the Web as a whole.

These companies may use the information they collect from your visits to this and other websites (not including your name, address, e-mail address or telephone number) to provide you with advertisements about products and services that interest you.

## Google Analytics

Google Analytics is a statistical data analysis service provided by Google (privacy policy).  Shareitforpc.online uses this service to keep track of usage statistics.

Google Analytics uses cookies to help this website analyse statistical data on the use of the site (number of visits, average duration of visit, etc.). The information generated by the cookie (including your IP address) will be transmitted directly to and stored by Google on servers in the United States.

Google will use this information on our behalf for the purpose of generating statistical information about your use of Shareitforpc.online, Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. Google may transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf.

You can refuse to process data or information by rejecting the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however, if you do so, it will limit the full functionality of Shareitforpc.online.

By using this website, you consent to the processing of information by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. For more information click on the link below:

### [How Google uses data when you use our partner applications or websites](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/)

## 

On our website we offer you links and services related to the different social networks ( for example “I like” from Facebook). If you are a member of a social network and click on the appropriate link, the social network provider may link your profile data to information about your visit to that website.

In relation to the management of your data associated with the social profiles of www.shareitforpc.online, the exercise of the right of access will depend on the functionality of the social network and the possibilities of access to the information in the user profiles.

With regard to the rights of access and rectification we remind you that it can only be satisfied in relation to that information that is under the control of www.shareitforpc.online.

In addition, you can stop interacting with, following or receiving information from the social profiles of www.shareitforpc.online, remove the contents that no longer interest you or restrict whoever shares your connections, through the mechanisms stipulated in the different social networks.

The user will be able to access the privacy policies of each Social Network, as well as configure their profile to guarantee their privacy.

www.shareitforpc.online encourages users to familiarize themselves with the conditions of use of the various social networks before starting to use them.

Facebook: <https://www.facebook.com/help/323540651073243/>

Google: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

Twitter: <https://twitter.com/privacy>

## Intellectual Property and use of the contents

The website www.shareitforpc.online, including but not limited to programming, editing, compilation and other elements necessary for its operation, designs, logos, text and / or graphics are the property of the provider or if necessary has been expressly licensed or authorized by the authors.

www.shareitforpc.online grants the user a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial-ShareAlike 3.0 license, the exact terms of which can be found at [this link](https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-sa/3.0/es/). Any use not previously authorized by the provider will be considered a serious breach of the intellectual or industrial property rights of the author.

The designs, logos, text and / or graphics outside the provider and that may appear on the website belong to their respective owners, being themselves responsible for any dispute that may arise with respect to them. In any case, the provider has the express prior authorization of the same.

## Applicable Law and Jurisdiction

For the resolution of all disputes or issues related to this website or the activities carried out on it, Spanish law shall apply, to which the parties expressly submit.

## Acceptance and Consent

The User declares to have been informed of the conditions of protection of personal data, accepting and consenting to the processing of the same by the provider in the manner and for the purposes indicated in the legal notice.
